Guide to the A. Arthur Schiller Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XVII: Computer Projects
  - Celsus Concordance 1-2 (Box 47)
  - Julianus Concordance (Box 48)
  - Pomponius Concordance (Box 49)
  - Sententia Hadriani Concordance (Box 49)
- Series XVIII: Printed Materials
  - Books by and with contributions by A.A. Schiller (1) (Box 50)
  - Books by and with contributions by A.A. Schiller (2) (Box 51)
- Series XIX: Microfilms. Card Files
  - Roman and Greek Law (Box 52)
  - Card Files: (Box 53)
    - Roman and Greek Law (Box 53)
  - Card Files: (Box 54)
    - Roman and Greek Law (Box 54)
  - Card Files: (Box 55)
    - Roman and Greek Law (Box 55)
  - Card Files: (Box 56)
    - Roman and Greek Law (Box 56)
    - Slips and Outline Roman Law (Box 56)
  - Card Files: (Box 57)
    - Roman and Greek Law (Box 57)
    - T&C Bibliography and Sources (Box 57)
  - Card Files: (Box 58)
    - Roman and Greek Law (Box 58)
    - T&S (Box 58)
  - Card Files: (Box 59)
    - Roman Law (Box 59)
    - Greek Law (Box 59)
  - Card Files: (Box 60)
    - African Law (Box 60)
  - 61. Card Files: (Box 61)
    - Papyri Budge Indexes (Box 61)
  - 62. Card Files: (Box 61)
    - Key-Punched Cards; Program (Box 61)
  - 63. Card Files: (Box 62)
    - Key-punched cards; Pomponius (1) (Box 62)
  - 64. Card Files: (Box 62)
    - Key-Punched; Pomponius (2) (Box 62)
  - 65. Card Files: (Box 62)
    - Key-Punched Cards;.Pliny (Box 62)
  - 66. Card Files: (Box 63)
    - Key-Punched Cards; African Roman Complete (Box 63)
    - Key-Punched Cards;.:Julianus (1) (Box 63)
  - 67. Card Files: (Box 63)
    - Key-Punched Cards; Julianus (2) (Box 63)
  - 68. Card Files: (Box 63)
    - Key-Punched Cards; Julianus (3) (Box 63)
  - 69. Card Files: (Box 64)
    - Key-Punched Cards; Julianus (4) (Box 64)
  - 70. Card Files: (Box 64)
    - Key-Punched Cards; Julianus (5) (Box 64)
  - 71. Card Files: (Box 64)
    - Key-Punched Cards; Julianus (5) (Box 64)
  - 72. Card Files: (Box 65)
    - Key-Punched Cards Julianus (7) (Box 65)
    - Sententiae Hadriani (Box 65)
    - Miscellaneous Program (Box 65)